<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:background="@drawable/backdash">

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="FAQ"
        android:textSize="40sp"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:textColor="#1f22b9"/>

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="->Is it possible to link Mobile Number with Aadhaar through OTP? What is the procedure to link Mobile Number with Aadhaar?\n

As per DoT Directive, some Telecom Operators have started linking of SIM with Aadhaar via OTP based authentication. To know more about the process, please contact your respective Telecom Service Provider.
\n
->What is OTP?
 It is an one-time temporary password (OTP), that is generated by an algorithm and valid only for 30 seconds. Because of this time variable characteristic, it is called OTP.
OTP is 8 digit long numeric string.
OTP is personal to the resident and is uniquely generated every 30 seconds for each resident separately.
With time-based OTP, the TOTP validation server and token generation app(like mAadhaar) use their respective system times to generate OTPs. The TOTP algorithm assumes that the system times are synchronized.
\n
->Why to use OTP?
 OTPs avoid a number of shortcomings that are associated with traditional SMS based OTP. The most important shortcoming that is addressed by TOTPs is that resident will not be dependent on mobile network for SMS delivery. Generating and sending OTP requires users to go through a completely unrelated workflow.
\n
->How OTP is generated?
OTP is generated in mobile application like mAadhaar. However, the Client mobile device’s time should be in sync with IST time-zone.
\n
->How to configure as User?
1.Download App android mobile application
2.Enter Your Aadhar Number with Registered Phone Number.
3.your OTP should be visible and is valid for 60 seconds.
\n

->How to configure as DoT Employee?
1.Download App android mobile application
2.Enter your provided login creditials to sign in.
3.Enter Adhar Number You want to check.
4.Check for Adhar exceeding 9 mobile connections"
            android:padding="15dp"
            android:fontFamily="sans-serif-smallcaps"
            android:textSize="20sp"

            />
    </ScrollView>

</LinearLayout>
